The Gilbert and Lila Silverman Fluxus Collection Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series XI: Miscellaneous Publications and Working Material
  - Exhibition Merchandise, 2003; Ten promotional t-shirts for the exhibition What’s Fluxus? What’s not! Why. at the Centro Cultural Banco de Brasil. (Box 409, Box XI.13)
I 1160–1177 71
I 1178–1198 72
I 1199–1222 73
I 1223–1243 74
I 1244–1268 75
I 1269–1272,1275–1284 76
I 1274 77
I 1285–1302,1304–1315 78
I 1316–1341 79
I 1342–1373 80
I 1374–1385 81
II 1 82
II 2 83
II 3 84
II 4 85
II 5 86
II 6 87
II 7 88
II 8 89
II 9 90
II 10 91
II 11 92
II 12 93
II 13 94
II 14 95
II 15 96
II 16 97
II 17 98
II 18 99
II 19 100
II 20 101
II 21 102
II 22 103
II 23 104
II 24 105
II 25 106
II 26 107
II 27 108
II 28 109
II 29 110
II 30 111
II 31 112
II 32 113
II 33 114
II 34 115
III 1 116
III 2 117
III 3 118
III 4 119
III 5 120
III 6 121
III 7 122
III 8 123
IV.A 1–22* 124
IV.B 1–21 125
IV.B 22–54,56–57 126
IV.B 58–74 127
IV.B 75–99 128
IV.B 100–123 129
IV.B 124–158 130
IV.B 159–182 131
IV.B 183–202 132
IV.B 203–215 133
V.A.1 1–24 134
V.A.1 23 135
V.A.1 25–50 136
V.A.1 51 137
V.A.2 1–42 138
V.A.2 43–75 139
V.A.2 76–94 140
V.B.1 1–24,26–27 141
V.B.1 28–54 142
V.B.1 55–72 143
V.B.1 73–108 144
V.B.1 109–136 145
V.B.1 137–145 146
V.B.1 146–147,149–183 147
V.B.1 184–200, 202-217 148
V.B.1 218–247 149
V.B.1 248–273,275–279 150
V.B.1 280–303 151
V.B.1 304–340 152
V.B.1 341–372 153
V.B.1 373–408 154
V.B.1 409–437 155
V.B.1 438–473 156
V.B.1 474–501 157
V.B.1 502–528 158
V.B.2 1–18 159
V.B.2 19–30 160
V.D.1 1–3 161
V.D.1 4–6 162
V.D.1 7–8 163
V.D.2 1–21 164
V.D.2 22–34 165
V.D.2 35–56 166
V.D.3 1–22 167
V.D.3 23–35 168
V.D.4 1–3 168
V.D.4 4–11 169
V.D.5 1–9 170
V.D.5 10 171
V.E 1,3,5,7,9,11,14–31 172
V.E 32–61 173
V.E 62–77 174
V.F 1-2,4–18 175
V.F 3 176
V.G 1–28 177
V.H 1–38 178
V.I 1–23 179
V.I 24–30 180
V.I 31–37 181
V.I 38–47 182
VI.A 1–12 183
VI.A 13–28 184
VI.A 29–44 185
VI.A 45–64 186
VI.A 65–70,72–78 187
VI.B 1–11 187
VI.B 12,14–25 188
VI.B 26–47 189
VI.B 48,50–65 190
VI.B 66–73 191
VI.C 1–6 191
VI.C 7–31 192
VI.C 32–46 193
VI.C 1–2 193
VI.D 3–7 194
VI.D 8–12 195
VI.D 13–18 196
VII.A 1–20 197
VII.A 21–43 198
VII.A 44–76 199
VII.A 77–94 200
VII.A 95–105 201
VII.A 106–136 202
VII.A 137–162 203
VII.A 163–185 204
VII.A 186–200 205
VII.A 201–220 206
VII.A 221–234 207
VII.A 235–241,243–254 208
VII.A 255–275 209
VII.A 276–293 210
VII.A 294–304 211
VII.A 305–316 212
VII.A 317–323,325–335 213
VII.A 336–364 214
VII.A 365–379 215
VII.A 380–398 216
VII.A 399–419 217
VII.A 420–440 218
VII.A 441–471 219
VII.A 472–488 220
VII.A 489–504 221
VII.A 505–524 222
VII.A 525–534 223
VII.A 535–549 224
VII.A 550–574 225
VII.A 575–594 226
VII.A 595–607 227
VII.A 608–627 228
VII.A 628–649 229
VII.A 650–663 230
VII.A 664–690 231
VII.A 691–708 232
VII.A 709–728 233
VII.A 729–745 234
VII.A 746–778 235
VII.A 779–798 236
VII.A 799–817 237
VII.A 818–835 238
VII.A 837–847 239
VII.B 1–13 240
VII.B 14–24 241
VII.B 25–40 242
VII.B 41–52 243
VII.B 53–71 244
VII.B 72–86 245
VII.B 87–99 246
VII.B 100–114 247
VII.B 115–117 248
VII.B 118–138 249
VII.B 139–152 250
VII.B 153–161 251
VII.B 162–171 252
VII.B 172–182 253
VII.B 183–191 254
VII.B 192–199 255
VII.B 200–209 256
VII.B 210–220 257
VII.B 221–233 258
VII.B 234–245 259
VII.B 246–260 260
VII.B 261–270 261
VII.B 271–279 262
VII.B 280–288 263
VII.B 289–298 264
VII.B 299–312 265
VII.B 313–320 266
VII.B 321–332 267
VII.B 333–344 268
VII.B 345–360 269
VII.B 361–368 270
VII.B 369–383 271
VII.B 384–395 272
VII.B 396–409 273
VII.B 410–422 274
VII.B 423–430,432–434 275
VII.B 435–448 276
VII.B 449–458 277
VII.B 459–470 278
VII.B 471–479 279
VII.B 480–494 280
VII.B 495–507 281
VII.B 508–521 282
VII.B 522–533 283
VII.B 534–541 284
VII.B 542–555 285
VII.B 556–567 286
VII.B 568–570,572–580 287
VII.B 581–592 288
VII.B 593–601 289
VII.B 602–611 290
VII.B 612–622 291
VII.B 623–637 292
VII.B 638–650 293
VII.B 651–662 294
VII.B 663–677 295
VII.B 678–686 296
VII.B 687–699 297
VII.B 700–714 298
VII.B 715–725 299
VII.B 726–734 300
VII.B 735–744,746–748 301
VII.B 749–760 302
VII.B 761–777 303
VII.C 1–7 304
VII.C 8–14 305
VII.C 15–21 306
VII.C 22–27 307
VII.C 28–33 308
VII.C 34–41 309
VII.C 42–53 310
VII.C 54–69 311
VII.C 70–76 312
VII.C 77–84 313
VII.C 85–92 314
VII.C 93–99 315
VII.C 100–105 316
VII.C 106–111 317
VII.C 112–116 318
VII.C 117–120 319
VII.C 121–132 320
VII.C 133–147 321
VII.C 148–162 322
VII.C 163–180 323
VII.C 181–196 324
VII.C 197–210* 325
VII.D 1–13 326
VII.D 14–25 327
VII.D 26–30 328
VII.E.1 1–18 329
VII.E.1 19–43 330
VII.E.1 44–73 331
VII.E.1 74–90 332
VII.E.1 91–109 333
VII.E.1 110–133 334
VII.E.1 134–158 335
VII.E.1 159–181 336
VII.E.1 182–202 337
VII.E.1 203–236 338
VII.E.1 237–267 339
VII.E.2 1–14 340
VII.E.2 15–29 341
VII.E.2 30–57 342
VII.E.2 58–89 343
VII.E.2 90–110 344
VII.E.3 1–15 345
VII.E.3 16–28 346
VIII.A 1–23 347
VIII.A 24–47 348
VIII.A 48–77 349
VIII.A 78–80 350
VIII.B 1–25 351
VIII.C 1–4 351
VIII.C 5–14 352
IX.A 1–17 353
IX.A 18-34 354
IX.A 35-51 355
IX.A 52-68 356
IX.A 69-80 357
IX.B 1–5 357
IX.B 6–16 358
IX.B 17–21 359
IX.C 1–12 359
IX.C 13–28 360
IX.C 29 361
IX.D 1–4 362
X.A 1–17 363
X.A 18–21 364
X.A 22 365
X.A 23–41 366
X.A 42–47 367
X.B 1 368
X.B 2–12 369
X.B 13 370
X.B 14–22 371
X.B 23–30 372
X.B 31 373
X.B 32 374
X.B 33–38,40–44,47–48 375
X.B 45 376
X.B 46 377
X.B 49 378
X.B 50–59,61–63 379
X.B 60 380
X.B 64–69 381
X.B 70 382
X.B 39, 71 383
X.B 72–80 384
X.B 81–82 385
X.B 83–84 386
X.B 85–87,89 387
X.B 88,90 388
X.B 91 389
X.B 92 390
X.B 93 391
X.B 94 392
X.B 95 393
X.B 96 394
X.B 97,99–105,107–111 395
X.B 98 396
X.B 106 397
X.B 112–113 398
X.B 114–128 399
X.B 129 400
X.C 1–14 401
XI 1 402
XI 2 403
XI 3 404
XI 4 405
XI 5 406
XI 8 407
XI 12 408
XI 13 409
I 99*,204*,205*,793*-798*,828*,856*,969* 410
I 1049*,1050*,1273* 411
IV.B 55* 411
V.B.1 25* 411
V.E 4*,6*,8*,10*,12*,13* 411
VI.A 71* 411
VI.B 13*,49* 411
VII.A 324* 411
I 169* 412
V.C 1*–2* 413
V.C 3*–7* 414
V.C 8*–13* 415
V.C 14*–19* 416
V.C 20*–22* 417
V.C 23*–25* 418
V.C 26*–28* 419
V.C 29*–31* 420
V.C 32*–34* 421
V.C 35*–37* 422
VII.C 208* 423
VII.C 209* 424
VII.C 210* 425
XI 9* 426
XI 10* 427
I 206*,207*,925*,970*,1303* Flat File 2-3
IV.A 21*,22* Flat File 2-3
V.B.1 148*,201*,274* Flat File 2-4
V.E 2* Flat File 2-4
VII.A 242* Flat File 2-4
VII.B 571*,745* Flat File 2-4
VII.B 431* Flat File 2-5
XI 6*,7*,11* Flat File 2-5